Guide to the Ellen Van Volkenburg and Maurice Browne papers vvb
University of Michigan Library (Special Collections Research Center)
- Printed Material
  - Organizations and places
    - Community Arts Association, Santa Barbara, Summer 1923 (Box 39)
    - Dartington Hall, 1930s-1950s (Box 39)
    - Garrick Playhouse, Altrincham, Cheshire (Box 39)
    - L'Istituto Nazionale del Dramma Antico, Siracusa, 1932 (Box 39)
    - The Latin Press, 1935 and undated (Box 39)
    - New York Drama League (Box 39)
    - Pasadena Playhouse, 1937 (Box 39)
    - Progressive Arts League (of America) (Box 39)
    - School of the Arts of the Theatre, San Francisco, 1923-1924 (Box 39)
    - Tacoma Drama League, 1925-1926 (Box 39)
    - Theatre of the Golden Bough, Carmel, 1924-1925 (Box 39)
    - University of Utah, 1918-1919 (Box 39)
  - Publications
    - Theatre Arts Magazine, New York (Box 39)
    - The Little Review, Chicago, 1915; 3 items (Box 39)
  - Topical
    - Journey's End (Box 39)
    - Moral Re-Armament, 1949-1960 and undated (Box 39)
    - Puppets (Box 39)
    - Viceroy Sarah (Box 39)
  - People
    - Bottomley, Gordon, The Thrush review of "The Riding to Lithend", 1910 (Box 39)
    - Brooke, Rupert memorial (Box 39)
    - Fuller, Rosalind (Box 39)
    - Gollancz, Victor, On Reconciliation, 1948 (Box 39)
    - Greene, Alexander (Box 39)
    - Khan, G. Ahmad article, 1932-1933 (Box 39)
      Signed.
    - Knox, Emma (Box 39)
    - Lion, Leon M., 1928 (Box 39)
    - Meiklejohn, Helen (Box 39)
      Related Materials
      See note at the bottom of Dorothy Straight's letter in the Correspondence series.
    - Melnitz, William W. (Box 39)
    - Monroe, Dorothy, "Monsieur Blanc", 1925 (Box 39)
      Also known as Hill, Dorothy Elizabeth (Browne).
    - Morris, Marjorie (Box 39)
    - Nesbitt, Cathleen (Box 39)
    - Storrs, Sir Ronald (Box 39)
    - Straight, Beatrice (Box 39)
    - Thorndike, Sybil, 1938 (Box 39)
    - Tobey, Mark, 1934-1969 (Box 39)
    - Material about Ellen Van Volkenburg and Maurice Browne, 1933-1961 (Box 39)
    - Wigman, Mary (Box 39)
    - Wigman, Mary: Globe Theatre poster (Oversize 1)
- Realia
  - Paul Robeson breastplates, 1930; 3 items (Object 1)
    3 breastplates worn by Paul Robeson in Othello.
  - Leather pouch (Object 2)
  - Paper and bamboo puppet (Object 3)
  - Green plaster head from a figurine (Object 4)